One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Let's go! Shining! Running! Forever!
Keep pushing forward!
The bond that joins us will never break
and its light will shine on the end of our dreams.
Wake up! Wake up! Wake up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Freedom is our only compass we need. -We are best friends-
We'll be the ones to carve out our own route.
We spend all our days moving full speed ahead, -Go east, Go west-
each day brings something new and we leave nothing unfinished.
Every trial we overcome brings a chance for thrills. (I can't stay)
Tomorrow and each day after will be heated, intense.
A chain of excitements!
That's right! Shining! Running! Forever!
Trust your curiosity, follow your heart
and head for your goal, that's what adventure is all about!
Let's go shining! Running! Forever!
Spread open the chart of your dreams!
There's power hidden in the bond between us,
it'll help us grasp the end of our dreams.
Never! Never! Never! Never stop it!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Dressrosa
Flower Fields
Riku Royal Army Rebellion HQ
Everyone ready?
Yeah!
Flower Fields
(Current Location)
We will now take the underground passage,
Trading port
and go into the enemy trading port!
Our goal is one little girl.
Sugar!
She may be small, but she's no pushover!
We will knock Sugar out, and turn all the toys in the country back into humans!
It's so cramped!
Robiland and I will barely be able to fit in there.
Fraland, you'd better take
off your shoulders and arms.
I can't do that!
Hey, that tunnel is way too small for me-land.
We weren't thinking about big humans using it.
You'll just have to enter through the Toys' House.
The Toys' House lies beneath
the plateau of the royal palace.
It's where the toys go every night.
Human entry is forbidden.
House? The toys live there?
It's a house in name only.
There are no beds or anything.
There's just a passage to the underground.
Every night, the toys take that passage...
and work underground all night long.
So the toys out in town are dead tired all the time?
How awful! That's too awful for words!
A-Anyway...
Fraland can get to the Smile factory that way, right?
Correct. The entrances are each of the four cardinal directions.
However, they're all heavily guarded.
Just how I like it.
I'll cause a huge ruckus while I'm there!
W-Why would you do that?
That'll make things easier for you, right?
You mean...
While I'm distracting them, you take out Sugar!
Who's that?
Swimming briefs?
What's up with your head?!
Is that a weapon?
Or is he just dumb?
Hey, look at his forked chin!
No doubt about it!
That's Cyborg Franky of the Straw Hat Pirates!
Senor! You shouldn't just shove tomatoes into your mouth.
You'll get your face all messy!
Oh, he's so...
hard-boiled!
Don't cling to me, little girls.
Doflamingo Family (Diamante Army ♦ Officer)
Senor Pink
Go hang with a younger guy.
Oh no, Senor!
Don't be so cold, Senor!
You kids...
are not my type.
Senor!
Don't abandon me, Senor!
What's with that pervert?
You're one to talk!
Calling from the Toy House eastern entrance!
One of them's here!
You will let me in.
Weapons Left!
Fire!
One of the Straw Hat Pirates! It's Cyborg Franky!
Coup de...
Vent!
Would you look at that.
The fools have started rampaging.
It's your job to assist the
World Government's member nations, right?
So they've begun?
The Toys' House is under attack.
Don't worry about it!
The Straw Hats are after the Smile factory.
Even if they make it here...
You can just make them all toys! Right?
Nobody knows!
Nobody knows about you!
You're right.
Underground passage
We've almost reached the trading port.
Captain! Fraland has started his assault by the Toys' House!
I see.
I'll cause a huge ruckus while I'm there!
I hope he's alright.
No need to worry! He's a super-cyborg!
I've just received word that four of the
Family's officers are guarding the Toys' House.
O-Officers?
It had to be the Diamante Army, of all people!
They're martial artists.
They're pretty strong, right?
Their victory rate in the battle tournaments is 100%.
They're the Colosseum's greatest heroes.
100%?
You mean they've never lost?!
Exactly. So in other words,
Nobody knows the full extent of their power!
H-How big is the enemy's elite force, Leo?
10 officers govern over 2,000 henchmen scattered throughout this land.
In turn, those 10 officers answer to the 3 elite officers.
Each of whom governs their own specialized army.
First is the Trébol Army.
Trébol Army (Special Ability Team)
They're the Special Ability Team.
Sugar!
Sugar
Violet!
Violet
Giolla!
Giolla
Next is the Diamante Army.
Diamante Army (Battle Brigade)
They're martial artists.
Lao G!
Lao G
Machvise!
Machvise
Senor Pink!
Senor Pink
Dellinger!
Dellinger
The last one is the Pica Army.
Pica Army (Special Ops Unit)
They're the commando unit!
Gladius!
Gladius
Buffalo and Baby 5!
Buffalo
Baby 5
We've also confirmed two more who aren't in the country right now.
Elite officer Vergo
Elite Officer Vergo.
Officer Monet
And the officer, Monet.
So we won't have to worry about the martial artists!
Hang in there, Franky!
They're all strong.
You're kidding me!
We're sorry, Usoland!
Thank you.
Don't mention it.
We're here. This is the underworld, home to the trading port and the factory.
It's surprisingly noisy.
Are sounds from the surface leaking through?
Hey, who dropped the cargo?!
This toy got caught under it.
I-I'm so sorry!
I'll work harder, so please let me see my family!
Dumbass! Anyone who can't measure up is headed straight to the scrapyard!
Take him away!
W-Wait! I can still work!
Help!
Usopp.
Robin, did you...
Look.
I can still work! Help!
If you're gonna be so stingy, I'll cancel our deal!
Bastard, you're exploiting me!
If only you didn't have Joker backing you, I swear...
What is all this?
This is a full-blown harbor town!
Suleiman begins his attack on Rebecca!
Go!
Die, Rebecca!
Suleiman, cut her head off!
Once a hero of the Dias Navy Battle, he is now wanted as a war criminal.
He is a fearful underworld killer!
"Dias Navy Battle" A-rank War Criminal
Suleiman the Beheader
The way he carries himself is like a lifeless ghost.
I did everything for my country.
I loved my homeland.
What about you?
It must be difficult to live surrounded by people who despise you.
I don't care how difficult it is.
I don't care who hates me.
I want to live with Soldier-san!
She just won't die!
Including the hateful Rebecca, about 30 people remain in Block D!
Another person is out!
I mean animal!
Adventurer, Yonta Maria Great Fleet
Orlumbus
It's killed dozens of people,
and stained the ring with blood!
The gladiator lion, Agyo, has just...
fallen to Orlumbus' whip.
He's strong.
Admiral!
Pirate, Cavendish
Will one of the favorites win?!
Or will it be a dark horse?!
The Fire Demon
Damask
This is the last battle before the finals!
The Witch Doctor
Mummy
Who is going to take the head of...
King Riku's granddaughter?!
Soldier-san, where are you right now?
Please don't die.
That's all I ask.
Beneath Dressrosa, Underground Trading Port
The soldier's gone?
Isn't he the captain?
The captain has the important task of killing Doflamingo the moment Operation SOP succeeds.
He took a few Tontattans and headed to the palace.
Good luck, captain!
Yeah!
We've got the hero Usoland with us.
Usoland, please lead Operation SOP and help us knock Sugar out.
Isn't that the most important job?!
We're here right now.
All the bridges are movable.
Lift
Trebol
Sugar
Underground
Passage
Factory
Officers' Tower
And that building in the distance...
that looks like a sea anemone...
That's the Officer's Tower.
That's where Sugar is.
Hey, who's that slacking off over there?!
They've found us! It's over!
What ship are you lot from?!
No, wait, I'm just passing by!
Only the negotiators are allowed off the ships.
Inhel.
Got it.
The fairies are here!
They stripped us of everything!
Tontatta Combat!
Tail Hammer!
T-They're buried in the ground!
Change into these, Usoland, Robiland.
I must say, you're really quick-witted.
Pretending that you were scared to distract the enemy..
Speaking of, do you all have such strength?
Yes, we all can do that much.
But Noland's clan can kill Sea Kings.
We don't even compare.
What kind of monster do these guys think I am?
But I might be able to win without fighting.
Okay everyone, I, Usoland will take command!
Our opponent is a little girl!
Let's gang up on her and scare her!
Follow me!
Yes, sir!
Oh... No... wait...
Go on ahead!
Yeah!
Let's go to the Officer's Tower!
Royal Palace
Officer's
Tower
The Toys'
House
Factory
Lift Junction
Trading
Port
Royal Palace, Toys' House, Trading Port,
Officer's Tower, and Lift Junction layout
Hurry and get on!
There's an intruder in the Toys' House!
The Straw Hat Pirates have appeared.
They're fighting Senor Pink-sama at the east entrance.
They're after the factory down here.
Fraland...
I heard you get a bonus for taking them down.
Seriously? How much?!
The reward'll probably be massive.
Let's head up.
Really?
It's a rumor.
Really now, where'd you get that info from?
At this rate, we'll just keep going back and forth between the Toys' House and underground.
Let's take over the lift.
You guys wait here.
Surrender now.
I'm taking over this lift.
This guy is...
The Thunder Soldier from the Colosseum!
How did he get here?
He dodged it!
You're too slow!
Damn you!
Soldier-san hit me! That's domestic violence!
No it isn't!
I don't want to hit you!
Then stop before you hit me!
You won't grow without any danger!
Concentrate, Rebecca!
A human's instincts are far greater than you think!
Bring them out!
Believe in the strength of humans!
But you're a toy, Soldier-san!
Stop complaining!
I don't want to learn how to fight anymore!
Why can't you always protect me?
I'm a toy.
If I'm exposed to the rain or wind, I'll rust.
I don't know when my body will reach its limit.
Stand up, Rebecca!
Become strong!
My body isn't made to fight.
Maybe toys are destined...
to break before children become adults.
Forgive me, Rebecca.
Your clumsy father was only able to teach you to fight.
Was he always this strong?!
What are you after?!
What could a toy like you want?!
I want a peaceful country...
where my daughter can be happy!
I'll have you give Dressrosa back to the Riku Royal Family!
King Riku?
What bullshit are you spouting!?
I'll gladly give my life for that cause.
Corrida Colosseum
What's just happened?!
That was quick.
What the?!
I didn't see a thing.
I'd heard the stories, but...
Oh my, everyone's gone down!
All the survivors of Block D have fallen down, and for some reason, none of them are standing up!
Is this for real?!
The assault on Block D happened in an instant!
No, wait!
Someone's trying to stand up!